<ReleaseNotes>
	<Changeset component="org.gcube.portlets.user.databases-manager-portlet.1-8-0"
		date="2017-06-12">
		<Change>Support Java 8 compatibility [ticket #8432]</Change>
	</Changeset>
	<Changeset component="org.gcube.portlets.user.databases-manager-portlet.1-7-0"
		date="2017-02-15">
		<Change>Fixed groupId</Change>
	</Changeset>
	<Changeset component="org.gcube.portlets.user.databases-manager-portlet.1-6-0"
		date="2016-12-01">
		<Change>Porting to DataMiner service</Change>
	</Changeset>
	<Changeset component="org.gcube.portlets.user.databases-manager-portlet.1-5-0"
		date="2016-10-01">
		<Change>Updated dependencies</Change>
	</Changeset>
	<Changeset component="org.gcube.portlets.user.databases-manager-portlet.1-4-0"
		date="2016-07-15">
		<Change>Updated to Liferay 6.2</Change>
	</Changeset>
	<Changeset component="org.gcube.portlets.user.databases-manager-portlet.1-3-0"
		date="2014-12-05">
		<Change>ufor the submitQuery the file result management has been
			modified. The file is retrieved from the statistical.
			GWTdbManagerServiceImpl, GxtBorderLayoutPanel, ComputationOutput,
			SubmitQueryResultWithFileFromServlet modified.
			UriResolver used to generate an http link from smp url. Dependency added in the
			pom file.
		</Change>
		<Change>bug fixed for ehcache. The operation of the cache-diskstore
			pair seems not operate in a correct way when retrieving a big object
			composed of many data. When a big object is retrieved, some data,
			previously stored, have been corrupted.
			In order to solve the problem, a safe procedure has been implemented
			that, once recovered the data from cache, checks if the data are
			corrupt. If yes, they need to be recovered again.GWTdbManagerServiceImpl class modified.
		</Change>
		<Change>GWTdbManagerServiceImpl class modified:
			1)parameter eternal changed from false to true value in such a way data never
			expire.Data will be always in cache.
			2) method insertDataIntoCache changed in order to add a check on key.
			If cache contains it then the related element is added in cache.
		</Change>
		<Change>samplings and submitQuery changed in order to return as a
			result a map with column values truncated to 255 characters and a
			file with the whole columns values in order to manage so to manage
			big data properly and the conversion of a geometry data type in a
			multipolygon representation applying the function st_astext().Classes
			GWTdbManagerServiceImpl, GxtBorderLayoutPanel and
			SamplingResultWithFileFromServlet changed in order to manage the
			truncated map and the file recovered from the statistical through a
			smt url and converted in a http url.
		</Change>
		<Change>dependencies modified in pom file:
			- dependency xalan modified in provided in order to use the lib
			available in the portal.
			- dependency jakarta-regexp added in order to not use the package
			regexp in xalan
			- removed an aslcore dependency because duplicated.
		</Change>
		<Change>
			- total number rows added in the header of the result related to the
			submit Query operation: classes ComputationOutput,SubmitQueryResultWithFileFromServlet,GxtBorderLayoutPanel,
			GWTdbManagerServiceImpl modified.
			- class Result modified in order to implemet IsSerializable and not
			Serializable 
			- pom file modified in order to use gwt 2.6.1 with scope compile and
			not use gwt from the portal bom file.
		</Change>
	</Changeset>
	<Changeset component="org.gcube.portlets.user.databases-manager-portlet.1-2-0"
		date="2014-10-27">
		<Change>user timeout session management generating a
			SessionExpiredException in order to show the session checker dialog
			and redirect to login.
		</Change>
		<Change>
			Class StatisticalManagerException created in order to manage
			exceptions generated from the statistical
		</Change>
		<Change>
			caching on sampling, smartSampling and submitQuery requests
			added.
		</Change>
		<Change>
			bug fixed in servlet in sbmitQuery method generated when a map
			is
			retrieved from a statisticalmanager and a user clicks cancel
			button.
		</Change>
		<Change>
			data refresh added for sampling, smartSampling and submitQuery
			operations.
		</Change>
		<Change>
			cache name changed in DBCache.
		</Change>
		<Change>
			batch processing (thread) added to recover all data in the
			tree and the
			tables list.
		</Change>
		<Change>
			data cached adding in a key the scope within a user uses the
			portlet.
		</Change>
		<Change>
			data refresh improved in the tree panel in order to
			implement
			the cascade refresh using a thread.Queue mechanism added to make
			asynchronous the communication with the ThreadDataLoader.
		</Change>
		<Change>
			For the functionality of TablesList the "canc" button of the
			window that displays the tables list has been removed and has been
			added icon at the top of the window (as well as in submitQuery and
			Samplings dialogs). In addition, on top of the window has been also
			removed icon that minimizes window and has been added icon that
			maximizes the window.
		</Change>
		<Change>
			bug fixed in class GxtBorderLayout in order to manage the copy
			of grid
			elements correctly. An element copy has been managed setting a
			grid
			property named disbleTextSelection and not through the double
			click
			and the edit event.
		</Change>
		<Change>
			counter added in order to count the cache hit number and the
			satistical manager computation number, the cache query sampling hit
			number and the satistical manager query sampling computation number
			to perform statistics about the effectiveness of the cache.
		</Change>
		<Change>
			for submitQuery operation attributes names added in the csv
			file.
		</Change>
		<Change>
			bug fixed for the submit query operation if at the same time a
			refresh query operation is performed. GWTdbManagerServiceImpl and
			GxtBorderLayput classes modified.
		</Change>
		<Change>
			top header in the portlet made invisible. GxtBorderLayout
			class modified.
		</Change>
		<Change>
			bug fixed in DatabasesResourcesManager component and related
			to samplings operations and the related column values truncation.If
			quote is truncated the parsecvsString in servlet does not work fine.
			Row, GxtBorderLayoutPanel, GWTdbManagerServiceImpl,
			GxtBorderLayoutPanel classes modified to manage in a correct way the
			exception generated in class Row while parsing a csv row in a values
			list for samplings operations.
		</Change>
	</Changeset>
	<Changeset component="org.gcube.portlets.user.databases-manager-portlet.1-1-0"
		date="2014-09-10">
		<Change>samplings operations, show create table and table details made
			available. Interface enhancement
		</Change>
	</Changeset>
	<Changeset component="org.gcube.portlets.user.databases-manager-portlet.1-0-0"
		date="2014-06-30">
		<Change>first release</Change>
	</Changeset>

</ReleaseNotes>