<ReleaseNotes>
	<Changeset
		component="org.gcube.dataaccess.algorithms.database-rm-algorithms.1-4-0"
		date="2016-12-01">
		<Change>Updated algorithms to DataMiner</Change>
	</Changeset>
	<Changeset
		component="org.gcube.dataaccess.algorithms.database-rm-algorithms.1-3-0"
		date="2014-12-05">
		<Change>algorithm SubmitQuery modified in order to pass the string
			pathfile to the submitQuery method of class DatabaseManagement in
			order to generate a file and retrieve it from the statistical manager
			with the map as output.
		</Change>
		<Change>Algorithms RandomSampleOnTable, SampleOnTable,
			SmartSampleOnTable and SubmitQuery modified in order to manage the
			file as output.
		</Change>
		<Change>total number rows returned as output for the result of the
			submit Query operation: algorithm SubmitQuery modified
		</Change>
	</Changeset>
	<Changeset
		component="org.gcube.dataaccess.algorithms.database-rm-algorithms.1-2-0"
		date="2014-10-27">
		<Change>some algorithms modified to cope modifications applied in the
			database-resource-manager component and regarding the management of
			the same access
			point for a resource and the database connection
			shutdown.
		</Change>
	</Changeset>
	<Changeset
		component="org.gcube.dataaccess.algorithms.database-rm-algorithms.1-1-0"
		date="2014-09-10">
		<Change>SubmitQuery algorithm updated because input parameters
			in the
			SubmitQuery method of DatabaseManagement class have been updated
		</Change>
		<Change>timer added in the SubmitQuery algorithm that stops the query
			execution after 30 minutes
		</Change>
		<Change>hibernate bug fixed and related to a join tables with same
			columns names. Bug resolved using JDBC. GetConnection
			method changed
			in the SubmitQuery algorithm to create
			the connection with JDBC
		</Change>
		<Change>method shutdown of algorithm SubmitQuery implemented in order
			to allow a user to cancel a submit query operation
		</Change>
		<Change>bug fixed when two algorithms are submitted concurrently.Bug
			related to map result's name. Bug fixed generating the name as
			ResultsMap"+UUID.randomUUID()
		</Change>
		<Change>classes SubmitQuery, SampleOnTable, SmartSampleOnTable,
			RandomSampleOnTable modified in order to not make available the
			file
			as result
		</Change>
		<Change>file DestinationDBHibernate modified to insert the property on
			the timeout
		</Change>
		<Change>bug fixed on table names that are keywords.Method
			GetTableDetails corrected to consider the name as schema.table for
			postgres and database.table for mysql
		</Change>
	</Changeset>
	<Changeset
		component="org.gcube.dataaccess.algorithms.database-rm-algorithms.1-0-0"
		date="2014-06-09">
		<Change>first release</Change>
	</Changeset>

</ReleaseNotes>