<ReleaseNotes>
	<Changeset component="org.gcube.execution.RRGCubeBridge.1-9-0" date="2014-07-02">
   		<Change>Added support for SRU datasources</Change>
   		<Change>Optimized code on fields retrieval</Change>
	</Changeset>
	<Changeset component="org.gcube.execution.RRGCubeBridge.1-8-0" date="2014-06-03">
   		<Change>Resources are retrieved by resource-manager</Change>
   		<Change>Changed logger to slf4j</Change>
	</Changeset>
	<Changeset component="org.gcube.execution.RRGCubeBridge.1-7-0" date="2014-03-28">
   		<Change>Changed to support non-tree collections (like Smartfish collection)</Change>
   		<Change>Added support for new type of indexservice that merges FT and FW</Change>
	</Changeset>
	<Changeset component="org.gcube.execution.RRGCubeBridge.1-6-0" date="2014-02-07">
   		<Change>RR retrieves collections that are specified as generic resources with secondary type DataSource and stores their type (if any)</Change>
	</Changeset>
	<Changeset component="org.gcube.execution.RRGCubeBridge.1-5-0" date="2013-10-10">
   		<Change>Removed ghn dependencies</Change>
   		<Change>Fixed delete searchable and presentable fields functionality</Change>
	</Changeset>
	<Changeset component="org.gcube.execution.RRGCubeBridge.1-4-3" date="2013-05-13">
   		<Change>ForwardIndexNode support</Change>
	</Changeset>
	<Changeset component="org.gcube.execution.RRGCubeBridge.1-4-2" date="2013-04-01">
   		<Change>Removed CM dependencies</Change>
	</Changeset>
   	<Changeset component="org.gcube.execution.RRGCubeBridge.1-4-1" date="2013-02-12">
   		<Change>FullTextIndexNode support</Change>
   	</Changeset>
	<Changeset component="org.gcube.execution.RRGCubeBridge.1-4-0" date="2012-11-26">
   		<Change>Added harvesting of tree manager collections</Change>
   		<Change>Harvesting of deployed packages of a Hosting Node has been re-enabled after RRModel database schema changes</Change>
   	</Changeset>
	<Changeset component="org.gcube.execution.RRGCubeBridge.1-3-2" date="2013-02-12">
   		<Change>FullTextIndexNode support</Change>
   </Changeset>
	<Changeset component="org.gcube.execution.RRGCubeBridge.1-3-1" date="2012-10-22">
   		<Change>Removed harvesting of deployed packages of a Hosting Node because the large list of packages caused fail at bridging.</Change>
   		<Change>Static configuration resources are now loaded when field directory is missing</Change>
   </Changeset>
	<Changeset component="org.gcube.execution.RRGCubeBridge.1-3-0" date="2012-05-04">
   		<Change>Aligned to new datastore labels.</Change>
		<Change>Aligned to latest resource model (data sources and bound service instances)</Change>
		<Change>Removed logic which is now integrated into plugins.</Change>
   </Changeset>
   
    <Changeset component="org.gcube.execution.RRGCubeBridge.1-2-2" date="2012-4-5">
   		<Change>fix for ticket #404: scopes used while updating field generic resources are now the same as the scopes used during retrieval instead of the scopes specified in the generic resources themselves.</Change>
   </Changeset>
   
   <Changeset component="org.gcube.execution.RRGCubeBridge.1-2-1" date="2012-1-27">
   			<Change>Property pair representation for hosting nodes is aligned with latest version of RRModel.</Change>
   			<Change>pe2ng port property extraction from hosting nodes is now performed correctly.</Change>
   </Changeset>
   
   <Changeset component="org.gcube.execution.RRGCubeBridge.1-2-0" date="2011-11-04">
		<Change>Support for in memory prefetching of element subset for increased query and loading time performance.</Change>
		<Change>Support for in memory prefetching of element subset for increased query and loading time performance. Per-field representation or persisted model in separate 
		generic resources in order ensure model serialization remains scalable</Change>
	</Changeset>
	
	<Changeset component="org.gcube.execution.RRGCubeBridge.1-1-0" date="2011-09-02">
		<Change>Added element metadata support. Metadata contain either extra information on existing items or information on items not present in the infrastructure 
		anymore, such as inactive DataSources. Metadata contain implementation agnostic properties, which can be read by whichever repository provider is operating at the 
		given moment. Currently the only element metadata used concerns inactive DataSources. A grace period is defined for inactive DataSources, and after it has elapsed, 
		all searchables and presentables referencing such DataSources are purged from the corresponding fields. This functionality is performed by the updater in an extra 
		outgoing alignment step.</Change>
		<Change>GCube repository provider optionally reads configuration such as inactive DataSource grace period and generic resource name and secondary type. In the absence of such 
		configuration, the default values are used.</Change>
		<Change>Added support for automatic field-searchable-presentable creation. The aforementioned entities will be created by an updater which has the feature enabled.
		The feature can be enabled by the corresponding property in the gCube repository provider configuration file.</Change>
	</Changeset>	
	
	<Changeset component="org.gcube.execution.RRGCubeBridge.1-0-1" date="2011-07-29">
		<Change>Changed scope handling in order to solve #1705. In the context of a running container, the gHN scopes are being used except root infrastructure scopes.
		 In client mode, the previous behavior is retained, whereby the working scopes of the provider are the start scopes of the container, plus all VRE scopes under 
		 the latter.</Change>
		 <Change>Fixed scope assignment issue in getDataSource</Change>
	</Changeset>
	
   <Changeset component="org.gcube.execution.RRGCubeBridge.1-0-0" date="2011-07-01">
		<Change>First Release</Change>
	</Changeset>
</ReleaseNotes>

