<ReleaseNotes>
	<Changeset component="org.gcube.execution.gRS2.2-1-2" date="2014-10-31">
	    <Change>Fixed memory issue with tcp connections</Change>
	</Changeset>
	<Changeset component="org.gcube.execution.gRS2.2-1-1" date="2014-01-20">
	    <Change>Moved xstream version to 1.4.4.</Change>
	    <Change>Fixed a bug that cause HTTP protocol to fail due to Java 1.7 API changes</Change>
	</Changeset>
	<Changeset component="org.gcube.execution.gRS2.2-1-0" date="2012-10-20">
	    <Change>Extended RecordReaderDelegate in order to support setting window size to RandomReaders that is needed from ASLSearch</Change>
	</Changeset>
	<Changeset component="org.gcube.execution.gRS2.2-0-0" date="2012-07-04">
	    <Change>Performance improvements on the TCP transfer method</Change>
	    <Change>Exceptions can be transfered though the gRS2</Change>
	</Changeset>
	<Changeset component="org.gcube.execution.gRS2.1-3-0" date="2012-05-03">
	    <Change>support HTTP as gRS2 transfer method</Change>
	    <Change>Changes in reader iterators: hasNext() now closes reader after timeout expiration and always returns false from that point on. next() throws NoSuchElementException if hasNext() is false.</Change>
	    <Change>Revised network congestion prevention policy in TCPReaderMirror: No sleeps are performed between iterations anymore when throughput must be maximum. 
	    Long sleeps are performed when either the consumer does not need more result or when the producer does not have results available and the consumer still has results to process. 
	    Short sleeps are performed when the producer does not have results available but the producer could need additional result soon (i.e. its buffer is empty)</Change>
	</Changeset>
	<Changeset component="org.gcube.execution.gRS2.1-2-0" date="2012-02-17">
		<Change>Reader buffer capacity is now configurable. The default value is the capacity of the writer, as before.</Change>
	    <Change>Support for URL resolver</Change>
	</Changeset>
	<Changeset component="org.gcube.execution.gRS2.1-1-3" date="2011-07-01">
		<Change>TCP communication between a producer and a consumer is now gracefully closed in all cases if the consumer decides to close its reader without having read all available records</Change>
		<Change>Added optional inactivity option to keep-alive reader</Change>
	</Changeset>
	<Changeset component="org.gcube.execution.gRS2.1-1-2" date="2011-04-29">
		<Change>Added record hide/show functionality which enables clients to prevent records from being disposed while still being able to reattach the latter to the same buffer instance</Change>
	</Changeset>
	<Changeset component="org.gcube.execution.gRS2.1-1-1" date="2011-03-25">
		<Change>Fixed keep-alive reader issue</Change>
		<Change>Fixed random reader seek issue</Change>
		<Change>Added local file cleanup functionality to FileField definition</Change>
		<Change>Locator elevation utility renamed</Change>
	</Changeset>
	<Changeset component="org.gcube.execution.gRS2.1-1-0" date="2011-02-07">
		<Change>Updated interface access and core redesign</Change>
	</Changeset>
	<Changeset component="org.gcube.execution.gRS2.1-0-1" date="2010-10-08">
		<Change>Fixed lifecycle synchronization issue</Change>
		<Change>Fixed record statistics purging</Change>
		<Change>Fixed buffering tie-break</Change>
	</Changeset>
</ReleaseNotes>
