<ReleaseNotes>
	<Changeset component="org.gcube.dataaccess.database-resource-manager.1-3-0"
		date="2014-12-05">
		<Change>method submitQuery modified in class DatabaseManagement in
			order to return as output a file and a map. The map is truncated to
			1000 rows if the result has more than 1000 rows.
			method writeTableIntoFile reintroduced that performs the file writing and
			the map generation.
		</Change>
		<Change>method submitQuery modified in class DatabaseManagement
			adding
			the UUID string to the submitQuery result file QueryResult
			file
		</Change>
		<Change>samplings and submitQuery changed in order to return as a
			result a map with column values truncated to 255 characters and a
			file with the whole columns values in order to manage so to manage
			big data properly and the conversion of a geometry data type in a
			multipolygon representation applying the function st_astext() for a
			database postgres.
		</Change>
		<Change> writeSubmitResultIntoFile method modified removing special
			characters using regular expressions in order to write data in a file
			correctly.
		</Change>
		<Change> total number rows returned as output for the result of the
			submit Query operation:class DatabaseManagement modified
		</Change>
	</Changeset>
	<Changeset component="org.gcube.dataaccess.database-resource-manager.1-2-0"
		date="2014-10-27">
		<Change>class DBResource modified in order to remove for a resource
			duplicated access points elements that have the same endpoint,
			username and password values.
		</Change>
		<Change>method closeconnection in class DatabaseManager modified in
			order to close the SessionFactory. Sampler class modified.
		</Change>
		<Change>bug fixed and related to samplings operation to manage column
			uppercase names with a postgres database.
		</Change>
		<Change>for the getTableDetails operation column names recovered as
			defined in their database's schema. PostgresTableStructure class
			modified.
		</Change>
		<Change>bug fixed in class ConnectionManager for the submitquery
			operation modified in order to manage the data geometry recovering
			the related value as a sequence of hexadecimal characters and not as
			a parsed multipolygon value.
		</Change>
		<Change>bug fixed in class DatabaseManagement for the submitquery
			operation in order to truncate column values of the result to 255
			character.
		</Change>
		<Change>bug fixed in Sampler class in computeSmartSampleWithThreshold
			method. table name formatted as schema."table" in order to recover
			the rows.
		</Change>
		<Change>
			bug fixed for the submitQuery and sampling operation and
			related to
			column value truncated to 255 characters. If the final
			quote has been
			truncated the parsecvsstring method in the servlet does
			not work
			fine. Bug fixed adding the final quote. convertToJavaType
			method in
			DatabaseManagement class modified.
		</Change>
	</Changeset>
	<Changeset component="org.gcube.dataaccess.database-resource-manager.1-1-0"
		date="2014-09-10">
		<Change>File DestinationDBHibernate.cfg.xml in "cfg" folder of the
			project renamed in DestinationDBHibernateDBManager.cfg.xml and
			correction in method initDBSession of the ConectionMannaager class in
			order to specify this file name.
		</Change>
		<Change>bug fixed for the smart sampling on table scientific_names of
			col2oct2010.Table name is overwritten when two iterations are
			performed to extract 200 rows.Corrections in
			computeSmartSampleWithThreshold.
		</Change>
		<Change>input parameters updated in the SubmitQuery method of
			DatabaseManagement class.(input parameter on path file removed
			because unusable)
		</Change>
		<Change>bug hibernate on join tables with same column
			names.ConnectionManager and DatabaseManagement classes modified
			adding the method "executeQueryJDBC" in ConnectionManager, used only
			for the submitquery operation. The method uses JDBC.
		</Change>
		<Change>bug fixed in sampling operations with an attribute of geometry
			type that slows the result visualization. Attributes truncated to 255
			characters.
		</Change>
		<Change> bug fixed with the rand() function in the smart and random
			sample for a database mysql with the computeSmartSampleWithThreshold
			method
		</Change>
		<Change>bug fixed in Sampler and DatabaseOPerations classes to manage
			case sensitive tables for database Postgres and for GetTableDetails
		</Change>
		<Change>class DatabaseManagement modified in order to not make
			available the result in a file csv for submitquery and samplings
			operations
		</Change>
		<Change>added a timeout database connection</Change>
		<Change>bug fixed in samplings on table names that are keywords.The
			name considered is schema.table for postgres and database.table for
			mysql
		</Change>
		<Change>bug fixed in sampler in order to have an attributes header
			with the same order defined in the database schema
		</Change>
		<Change>bug corrected in "showCreateTable" method of
			MySQLTableStructure class.Result managed in a correct way using
			aliasToEntityOrderedMapResultTransformer class
		</Change>
	</Changeset>
	<Changeset component="org.gcube.dataaccess.database-resource-manager.1-0-0"
		date="2014-06-09">
		<Change>first release</Change>
	</Changeset>
</ReleaseNotes>